Hey, will you steam my uniform next?
Tu peux t'occuper du mien après ?
Interesting. Do you recall this conversation?
Tu te souviens de cette conversation :
"Leonard, wanna go halfsies on a steamer?"
"Leonard, tu veux investir dans un fer à vapeur ?"
"No, Sheldon, we don't need a steamer."
”Non, Sheldon. Nous n'en avons pas besoin."
Looks like that rumpled chicken's come home to roost.
Tu en as marre de porter un uniforme froissé ?
Hi. Here are the makeup sponges you asked for.
J'ai tes éponges a maquillage.
-Oh, thanks, I thought I had more. -Hmm.
Merci. Je croyais en avoir plus.
Damn, you've got more makeup than I do.
Tu as plus de maquillage que moi.
You've got better makeup than I do. Yeah, I'm borrowing this.
Et de meilleure qualité. Je t'emprunte ça.
Hey, hey, hey, this is my Comic-Con makeup.
Eh, c‘est mon maquillage pour les Comic-Con.
I love you, but there are some things a man doesn't share with his girlfriend.
Je t‘aime, mais un homme ne partage pas tout avec sa petite amie.
That's a wise policy.
Sage politique.
I once borrowed my sister's makeup for a costume contest...
J'ai emprunté le maquillage de ma sœur une fois
...got a terrible case of pink eye.
etj'ai eu une conjonctivite.
Yeah, well, luckily, I was going as a zombie, I won second place.
J'étais déguisé en zombie, je suis arrivé deuxième.
You guys just went to Comic-Con.
Vous rentrez d'un Comic-Con.
That was San Diego Comic-Con. This is Bakersfield Comic-Con.
C'était celui de San Diego. La, c‘est Bakersfield.
-Is that better? -Well, it's a lot smaller.
- C‘est mieux ? - C‘est plus petit.
It's about the comic books.
C‘est plus sur les comics, c‘est plus traditionnel.
So to answer your question, no, it's not better.
Pour te répondre, non, ce n‘est pas mieux.
Then why are you going?
Pourquoi y allez-vous alors ?
It's a comic book convention.
C‘est pour les comics.
Like pizza or particle accelerators...
Comme les accélérateurs de particules,
...even the stinky ones, still pretty good.
même les plus nuls sont bien.
Well, you guys have fun. I guess I'll see you Sunday.
Amusez-vous bien. A dimanche soir.
-Yeah. Oh, hang on a second. -Okay.
- Oh, attends. - Oui.
Hold this.
Tiens ceci.
-What was that for? -To show people when they don't believe me.
- Pourquoi ? - Pour qu'on me croie.
This is the best. You have booze with breakfast on Tuesday, you got a problem.
Tu picoles le matin en semaine, tu as un probléme.
You do it on the weekend, you got brunch.
Tu picoles le week-end, c‘est un brunch.
Sheldon doesn't believe in brunch.
Sheldon n'aime pas ça.
Can't stand a table where one person's having an omelet and another is having a sandwich.
Une personne qui mange une omelette,
That's not exhausting at all.
Ce n‘est pas du tout fatigant.
It's Leonard. He says they're on the road and headed for Bakersfield at warp speed.
C‘est Leonard. Ils sont en route àla Vitesse de la lumière.
Maybe it's the mimosa, but I'm gonna give the kid an LOL.
Ça doit être le mimosa, je vais lui envoyer un LOL.
Cute how excited they are.
Ils sont trop mignons.
You should have seen Howard sewing his costume all week.
Vous auriez dû voir Howard coudre son costume.
When did Howard learn to sew?
Il sait coudre ?
When he was a little boy, every couple of months he'd have to let his mom's pants out.
Quand il était petit, il devait élargir
I don't understand why they go to these conventions.
Pourquoi vont—ils a ces conventions ?
The four of them work at a major university, they're all smart...
Ils travaillent à l‘université, ils sont doués
...how can they be into something for 12-year-olds?
et ils aiment des bêtises pour ados.
I don't mind it. I think Howie's just in touch with his inner child.
Je comprends. Howie sait écouter l'enfant qui dort en lui.
Although when he's in Batman pajamas...
Même si son pyjama Batman
...sometimes it feels like I'm touching his inner child.
me donne l'impression de toucher l'enfant en question.
It's probably because they were bullied. In a world where you can't fight back...
C‘est sûrement parce qu‘ils ont été harcelés a l'école.
...superheroes provide meaningful wish-fulfillment.
Les super—héros donnent un sentiment de réussite.
Although if Danny Biffle didn't want to eat a mouthful of dirt...
Mais si Danny Biffle a mangé dela houe,
...he shouldn't have shown up to school wearing a bow tie.
c‘est qu'il portait un nœud pap' a l'école.
I've never even read a comic book. You guys?
-Je n'ai jamais lu un comic. - Moi non plus.
It's such an important part of their lives.
C‘est important pour eux.
-Maybe we should try reading some. -Seriously?
- On devrait en lire un. - Sérieusement ?
The comic book store isn't far from here.
La librairie n‘est pas loin.
That is an amazing idea.
C‘est une excellente idée.
Okay, how many of these have I had?
J'ai trop bu ou quoi ?
I think you should turn on the GPS.
Tu devrais allumer ton GPS.
It is on.
Il est allumé.
But the turn-by-turn voice option isn't on.
Mais l'option vocale est désactivée.
I know I'd feel more safe if you turn on the turn-by-turn voice option.
Je préférerais que tu allumes l'option vocale.
I love the turn-by-turn voice option.
J‘adore l'option vocale.
Has it really only been 10 miles?
Ça ne fait vraiment que 16 km qu'on roule ?
I'm turning it on, butjust to shut you up.
Je l'allume pour que tu la fermes.
GPS [IN SHELDON'S VOICE]: Leonard, bear left and continue on Interstate 210.
Leonard, tourne à gauche et prends l‘autoroute 210.
Ooh, sounds like that fellow knows what he's talking about.
Ce type sait de quoi il parle.
I'd put on my listening ears if I were you.
J‘ouvrirais mes oreilles, si j‘étais toi.
-What did you do? -I found a hack online.
- Qu'as-tu fait ? -J'ai piraté un logiciel.
l was able to upload MP3 recordings of my voice to your GPS.
J'ai pu intégrer des enregistrements de ma voix dans ton GPS.
-That is so cool. -Counterpoint, no, it's not.
- C‘est trop cool. - Non, ça ne l‘est pas.
6 PS : Continue on Interstate 210 for ï¬ve miles.
Continue sur l‘autoroute 210 pendant 8 km.
Here's an interesting fact about Interstates:
Voilà un fait intéressant sur les autoroutes.
-Really? -Shh!
Vraiment ?
He said it's interesting.
C‘est intéressant.
6 PS : Interstates are numbered as follows:
Elles sont numérotées de cette manière :
Even-numbered routes run east and west.
les nombres pairs indiquent celles allant vers l‘Est et l‘Ouest.
Odd-numbered routes run north and south.
Les nombres impairs celles allant vers le Sud et le Nord.
Three-digit route numbers indicate bypasses or spurs.
Les autoroutes a trois chiﬁres indiquent celles à rocades.
Look, Leonard, there's a bridge. Drive off it.
Regarde, un pont. Jetons-nous par-dessus bord.
You know, we're not that far from Vasquez Rocks.
Nous sommes a côté de Vasquez Rocks.
Oh, they shot a lot of Star Trek episodes out there.
Ils ont tourné de nombreux Star Trek là:—bas.
We got our costumes in the trunk...
Nos costumes sont dans le coffre.
...we could go there and have a little photo shoot.
On pourrait aller y faire des photos.
Great idea. I haven't had a carbohydrate in two weeks.
Bonne idée. Je ne mange pas de féculents depuis 15 jours.
These cheekbones need to be in front of a camera before I eat a pretzel and they're gone.
Ces pommettes doivent être prises en photo maintenant.
-It sounds fun. -Oh, smashing.
- Ça a l‘air amusant. - Formidable.
Now, Leonard, do you know how to get there?
Tu sais aller là:—bas ?
-No. -Yeah, well, luckily, someone in the car does.
- Non. - Heureusement, quelqu'un ici sait.
GPS: Recalculating.
En cours de calcul.
While we're waiting, do you know which president...
En attendant, savez-vous quel président
...signed the Interstate Highway System Act into law?
a mis en place le système des autoroutes ?
The answer coming up in 14 miles.
La réponse dans 22 km.
None of you will get it. It's Eisenhower.
Vous ne devinerez pas. C‘est Eisenhower.
Why are they staring?
Pourquoi nous regardent—ils ?
Who cares, just soak it in.
On s'en fiche. Faites comme moi.
Hello, boys.
Bonjour, messieurs.
Oh, hey.
Oh, salut.
Could you please stop staring? They're just girls.
Arrêtez. Ce sontjuste des filles.
It's nothing you haven't seen in movies or in drawings.
Vous en avez déjà vu dans les films.
-Hey, Stuart. -What brings you guys here?
- Salut. - Que faites-vous la ?
We were looking for a recommendation about comic books.
On cherche des conseils sur les comics.
Well, I recommend you don't open a store and sell them.
Je vous conseille de ne jamais en vendre.
We were wondering why the guys like this stuff, so we thought we'd try it.
On se demande pourquoi les garçons aiment ça. On veut essayer.
Oh, okay. What do you think you might be into?
Qu‘est—ce que vous préféreriez ?
Superhero? Fantasy? Graphic novels? Manga?
Les super—héros ? Le fantastique ?
I swear I will turn a hose on you.
Je vais vous arroser au jet.
What kind of comics do the guys like?
Qu'aiment les garçons ?
-All right, well, who's the best superhero? -Shh!
Qui est le meilleur super—héros ?
You can't ask a question like that in here. Are you trying to start a rumble?
Ne dis pas ça ici. Tu veux déclencher une bagarre ?
Well, what do you recommend?
Que nous conseilles-tu ?
Well, uh, let's see, you've got your basic clean-cut good guys:
Là, vous avez les bons garçons :
Superman, Spider-Man, Captain America.
Superman, Spider-Man, Captain America.
Then you have your darker anti-heroes:
La, il y a les anti—héros :
Your Batman, your Wolverine, Punisher.
Batman, Wolverine, Ie Punisher.
Ooh, I do love a bad boy.
J'aime les mauvais garçons.
As evidenced by your boyfriend and his fear of hamsters.
Comme le prouve la peur des hamsters de ton petit ami.
If I were you, I'd go for Fables number one.
Si j‘étais vous, je lirais Fables.
Artwork is sophisticated, it's intelligently written...
C‘est sophistiqué, bien écrit
...and it doesn't objectify...
- et la femme n‘est pas chosifiée. - Oh, Thor. Il est canon.
Yeah, he kind of is.
En effet.
And we're blending...
Et on étale,
...and we're blending, and we're done.
on étale et c‘est fini.
I know Mr. Data isn't supposed to smile, but here it comes.
Data n‘est pas supposé sourire, mais c‘est impossible.
Come on, guys, let's do this.
Venez, les gars. Allons-y.
Yeah, I'm sweating my bald cap off.
Je transpire sous mon crâne chauve.
What's our first pose gonna be?
Notre premiére pose ?
I say we begin with a classic Star Trek fight scene.
Une scène de combat classique.
I'll set the timer.
Je mets le retardateur.
Sheldon, how is that a fight pose?
On a dit une pose de combat.
Mr. Data's weapon is his mind.
L'arme de Data est son esprit.
I'm wielding it.
Je m‘exerce.
Phasers on the Borg!
Phaseurs sur le Borg !
Charlie's Angels!
Les Drôles de dames !
Okay, what's next?
Ensuite ?
Now let's do some sexy glamour shots.
Faisons une pose glamour.
I'll set the mood.
Je mets l‘ambiance.
Yeah, nice one.
Oui, super.
That's right.
C‘est ça.
Oh, my God. Leonard, someone's stealing your car!
Leonard, on voie ta voiture.
What? Hey! Hey, come back here!
Quoi ? Hé ! Revenez!
-Stop! -Stealing is against the law!
- Arrêtez ! - C‘est interdit par la loi !
I don't believe this.
Je n‘y crois pas.
Son of a bitch.
Enfoirés.
I'll call 911.
J‘appelle les secours.
Oh, no, my phone is in my other pants.
Mon téléphone est dans l‘autre pantalon.
Anybody got any ideas?
Une idée ?
Nope. The only thing left to do now is assign blame.
Non. Il ne nous reste plus qu'à porter des accusations.
Nice going.
Bonne idée.
What kind of a person steals another person's car in broad daylight?
Quel genre de personne voie des voitures en plein jour ?
What kind of person leaves his keys in the car?
laisse les clés dessus ?
Thought we agreed it's Koothrappali's fault.
Tout est la faute de Koothrappali.
You're right.
Tu as raison.
Nice going.
Bonne idée.
Car.
Une voiture.
What is wrong with people? Why don't they stop?
Pourquoi personne ne s'arrête ?
Maybe we're better off.
C‘est mieux comme ça.
What if we were to get in a car with a crazy person?
On pourrait tomber sur un fou.
Look at us, Sheldon. We're the crazy people.
Regarde—nous. C‘est nous, les fous.
Well, perhaps we should hold up a sign...
Nous devrions tenir une pancarte informant
...that assures passing motorists of our mental competence.
les automobilistes de nos capacités mentales.
Good idea. Why don't you get started on that?
Bonne idée. Commence à l‘écrire.
Come on, let's just start walking.
On n‘a plus qu'à marcher.
There's gotta be a gas station or something nearby.
Il doit bien y avoir une station service.
What, you thinkjust because you're wearing a captain's uniform you're in charge?
Avec ton uniforme, tu crois pouvoir donner les ordres ?
Yes.
Oui.
All right.
D‘accord.
Okay, I'm done.
C‘est bon. J'ai fini.
-How did you guys finish so fast? -I don't know, there were a lot of pictures.
- Vous avez déjà fini ? - Il y a beaucoup d‘images.
And one page only had the word "brakka-dooom!"
Et une page avaitjuste un mot.
Yeah, well, I have street smarts.
Je n‘étais pas trés bonne a l'école.
So, what'd you guys think?
Qu'en pensez-vous ?
-Well, there was a lot of action. PENNY: Hmm.
Il y a beaucoup d‘action.
And the story moved along at a brisk pace.
Et l'histoire a un rythme soutenu.
It was, overall, what's the word I'm looking for...?
C'était... Quel est le mot que je cherche ?
-Stupid? -So stupid.
- Stupide ? - Stupide.
I don't know how Leonard can get so caught up.
Je ne comprends pas Leonard.
It's crazy. They spend hours arguing about things that don't even exist.
Ils passent des heures a se disputer pour une fiction.
-What a waste of time. -I know.
- Perte de temps. - Oui.
A hammer so heavy that no one else can pick it up?
Un marteau si lourd que personne ne peut le porter ?
I don't think it's heavy, I think it's some sort of magic so only Thor can lift it.
Il n‘est pas lourd. Il est magique et seul Thor peut le porter.
That makes even less sense, I mean....
Ça a encore moins de sens.
Thor is a god. The hammer is his. Only he can use it.
Le marteau est a Thor. Lui seul peut s'en servir.
It's like Sheldon and his toothbrush.
C‘est comme Sheldon et sa brosse a dents.
Or his thin, beckoning lips.
Ou ses lèvres fines et attirantes.
Okay, hang on, what if Thor's hand is on the hammer?
Et si la main de Thor est sur le marteau ?
If he's touching it with his god magic, then does that mean I could lift it?
S'il le touche avec sa main, je peux le soulever ?
-No. -Yes.
- Non. -Oui.
Well, which is it?
Alors ?
-Maybe we missed something. -Let's read it again.
- On a raté quelque chose. - Il faut le relire.
-Okay. -Yeah.
- D‘accord. - Oui.
-You want some tea? -Good idea. I'll help you.
- Tu veux du thé ? - Bonne idée. Je t‘aide.
-Wait, I thought we were reading? -We are.
- On devait lire, non ? - C‘est le cas.
We're just, uh, giving you a head start.
On te laisse un peu d‘avance.
lwish my mom was here.
Ma mère me manque.
We could all hang out in her shadow.
On pourrait marcher dans son ombre.
Wool pants in the desert.
Un pantalon en laine dans le désert.
I feel like I've got poached testicles.
J'ai l'impression d‘avoir des testicules pochés.
Oh, you poor thing, you're sweating.
Pauvre petite chose, tu transpires.
That's so much worse than having your car stolen.
C‘est pire que de se faire voler sa voiture.
Insurance is gonna buy you a new car. It's not gonna de-funk myjunk.
L‘assurance te remboursera. Elle ne défroissera pas mon matériel.
Gentlemen, a little less bellyaching.
Messieurs, un peu moins de lamentations.
We're Starfleet officers and a member of the Borg Collective.
Nous sommes des officiers de Starfleet.
Please, Sheldon, I am so not in the mood.
Je ne suis pas d‘humeur.
Leonard...
Leonard,
...all our lives we have dreamed of finding ourselves...
toute notre vie, nous avons rêvé de nous retrouver
...inside one of the fantasy worlds we love.
dans un monde fantastique.
And look at us.
Et regarde—nous.
At this moment, we are, in fact, a Star Trek landing party...
En ce moment, nous sommes des éclaireurs de Star Trek
...stranded in an alien and unforgiving environment.
dans un environnement alien et hostile,
Relying only on our wits, our fortitude and our moxie.
ne comptant que sur notre esprit, notre courage et nos tripes.
As long as we have those things...
Tant que nous avons tout ça,
-...nothing can stop us-- MAN: Nerds!
- rien ne peut... - Bouffons !
I hate this planet.
Je hais cette planète.
It says right here on the hammer:
C‘est écrit sur le marteau :
"Whoever holds this hammer, if he be worthy, shall possess the power of Thor."
"Qui touche ce marteau s'il est valeureux, possède son pouvoir."
Hold on. Who decides who's worthy? Does the hammer decide?
Qui décide qui est valeureux ? Le marteau ?
-Yes! -No!
-Oui! -Non!
-It can't decide, it's a hammer. -You said it's a magic hammer!
- Impossible. C‘est un marteau. - Il est magique!
Yeah, but it can't make decisions.
Il ne prend pas de décisions.
If Harry Potter's wand can make decisions, why can't Thor's hammer?
La baguette d‘Harry Potter peut en prendre.
Okay, if you're gonna start comparing wands and hammers, I can't even take you seriously.
Si tu compares une baguette a un marteau, j'arrête de discuter.
Hello.
Bonjour.
Four glasses of water, please.
Quatre verres d'eau, s'il vous plaît.
Anything for you guys?
Vous voulez quelque chose ?
Can I use your phone? Our car got stolen.
Pourrions-nous téléphoner ? On nous a volé notre voiture.
Why don't you ask Scotty to beam you up?
Demandez à Scotty de vous téléporter.
Scotty was on the original series and we're Next Generation.
Il était dans la version originale, pas La Nouvelle Génération.
So joke's on you.
Votre blague est nulle.
We're not with him.
Nous ne sommes pas avec lui.
You can't pick something up in outer space.
Tu ne peux rien soulever dans l‘espace.
In space, there is no up.
Rien ne se lève dans l‘espace.
Oh, yeah? Then how does the sun come up every day?
Le soleil se lève bien tous les matins, non ?
Hard to argue with those kind of street smarts.
Difficile de débattre avec ces arguments.
Leonard and Sheldon have boxes of comics. Why don't we go look at those?
Allons lire les comics de Leonard et Sheldon.
Oh, great. And then you will see, lam not wrong.
Oui. Vous verrez, je n'ai pas tort.
If we were in outer space, anyone could pick up the hammer...
Dans l‘espace, on pourrait tous soulever le marteau,
...because it would be floating in a weightless environment.
car il flotterait en apesanteur.
Yeah, that's right, the slow reader used science. Suck on that.
Je lis lentement, mais j'ai étudié la physique, na.
-Was there anything valuable in the car? -Our clothes, our wallets, phones.
- Y avait-il des objets de valeur ? - Nos Vêtements et portefeuilles.
And about $300 worth of makeup...
Et 300 $ de maquillage,
...so this thief could look like anyone right now.
donc le voleur peut se faire passer pour un autre.
Makeup? Sure.
Du maquillage ? Bien sûr.
We're going to the Comic-Con in Bakersfield. They have a big costume contest.
Nous allons à un Comic-Con. Il y a un concours de déguisements.
It's cooler than it sounds.
C‘est plus cool que ça en a l'air.
I don't know, sounds pretty cool.
Sans aucun doute.
It is. It's notjust comic books.
Il y a plus que des comics.
They've got action figures, toys, a Tron themed dance party--
Des figurines, des jouets, une soirée dansante...
Okay, he gets how cool it is.
Il a compris.
lthinkl have all I need here. You guys need me to call someone?
Vous avez besoin queje passe un appel ?
I'm guessing your moms?
Vos mères, j‘imagine ?
Thanks, but we've got it covered.
Merci, mais on s'en occupe.
Okay, I just talked to my mom.
J'ai appelé ma mère.
She arranged for us to get a rental car.
Elle va nous louer une voiture.
Great, we can still make it to Comic-Con.
On peut aller àla conférence.
Are you kidding me? After all we've been through? I just want to go home.
Tu plaisantes ? Après tout ça ? J'ai envie de rentrer.
Don't be like that. Come on, Howard, talk to him.
Ne sois pas comme ça. Howard, parle-lui.
I'm with Leonard. I'm done.
Je suis d'accord avec Leonard. J'en ai assez.
Fine, then I guess it's two against two. How do we decide?
C‘est deux contre deux, alors. Qui décide ?
Actually, it's three against one.
C‘est trois contre un.
What? Well, what about the mission? You said we're a real-life landing party.
Quoi ? Et notre mission ? Nous sommes des éclaireurs.
We're an imaginary landing party.
Nous sommes des éclaireurs imaginaires.
Who had real-life garbage thrown at us by real-life strangers who think we're idiots.
Les vrais hommes d‘ici nous prennent pour des idiots.
And to tell you the truth, I'm starting to feel like one.
Je commence a me sentir bête.
I want to go home now.
Je veux rentrer maintenant.
Okay.
D‘accord.
Did we at least rent the car from Enterprise?
On loue une voiture chez Enterprise ?
Get it? Enterprise? Heh.
Pigé ? Enterprise ?
Screw you, that's funny.
Allez vous faire voir. C‘était drôle.
Well, what if the Hulk picked up Thor while Thor is holding the hammer?
Et si Hulk soulève Thor qui tient le marteau ?
-Yeah? -Then by the transitive property...
- Oui ? - Par la relation transitive
No, Hulk picked up Thor, Thor picked up the hammer.
Non. Hulk soulève Thor qui tient le marteau.
Hang on, ifl go to a bar and pick up a guy, and he picks up a girl...
Dans un bar, si je drague un gars qui drague une fille
...and then we all leave together, did I pick up the girl?
et qu'on repart ensemble, je drague la fille ?
Did that ever happen?
Ça t‘est déjà arrivé ?
Hey, we talking about me or are we talking about Thor?
On parle de moi ou de Thor ?
Well, I say that's the last time we ever go outside.
C‘est la dernière fois que nous sortons.
AMY: Look right here, Red Hulk is picking up Thor's hammer...
Ecoute. Hulk Rouge soulève le marteau,
...because Thor is touching it.
car Thor le touche.
PENNY: No, it's because they're in space!
Non, ils sont dans l'espace !
BERNADETTE: He's touching the strap. AMY: The strap is part of the hammer!
- Il touche la lanière. - C‘est le marteau.
Are they actually arguing about comic books?
Elles discutent de comics ?
No, that can't be right.
C‘est impossible.
Maybe Thor's Hammer is a new color of nail polish.
Le Marteau de Thor est peut-être le nom d'un vernis à ongles.
BERNADETTE: Then Red Hulk must be worthy!
- Hulk Rouge doit être valeureux. - Comment ça ?
BERNADETTE: You don't know his life.
Tu ne connais pas sa vie.
There's only one logical explanation: Somewhere in the desert...
Il n‘y a qu‘une seule explication. Dans le désert,
...we crossed into an alternate dimension...
nous sommes entrés dans une dimension
...where the women in our lives can finally appreciate great literature.
où les femmes semblent aimer la grande littérature.
If it's an alternate dimension...
Si c‘est une autre dimension,
...that sounds like ajob for a landing party.
il faut des éclaireurs.
Captain, what are your orders?
Capitaine, vos ordres ?
I say we investigate.
Menons une enquête.
Wait.
Attendez.
They might be hostile.
Elles peuvent être dangereuses.
Fine, but set them to stun.
Réglez—les en mode Taser.
If we vaporize Penny, I'll never find a girlfriend that pretty again.
Si on vaporise Penny, je n'en retrouverai jamais une aussi jolie.
GPS: Fun fact:
Fait amusant :
President Eisenhower signed the Federal Aid HighwayAct...
le président Eisenhower a mis en place ce système
...from his hospital room.
depuis sa chambre d‘hôpital.
You learn something new every day.
On en apprend tous les jours.
GPS: Say, can you name the four state capitals that are not served by the Interstate System?
Quels sont les quatre Etats qui ne sont pas traversés par ce système ?
-Ooh, another quiz? -Yes!
- Un autre quiz ? -Super.
[English - us - an]
[French]